<list>
  <de.ingrid.codelistHandler.model.CodeListUpdate>
    <id>10004</id>
    <type>ENTRYUPDATE</type>
    <entries>
      <de.ingrid.codelistHandler.model.CodeListEntryUpdate>
        <type>UPDATE</type>
        <entry>
          <id>5</id>
          <description></description>
          <localisations>
            <entry>
              <string>de</string>
              <string>Die Daten sind urheberrechtlich geschützt. Sie werden nur gegen Entgelt abgegeben. Es gelten die Regelungen der Richtlinie über Gebühren für die Bereitstellung und Nutzung von Geobasisdaten der Vermessungsverwaltungen der Länder der Bundesrepublik Deutschland (AdV-Gebührenrichtlinie in ihrer jeweils gültigen Fassung – AdV-GR: https://www.adv-online.de/AdV-Produkte/Bezugsbedingungen/). Für den Erwerb von Nutzungsrechten wenden Sie sich bitte an die Zentrale Stelle Geotopographie der AdV/Dienstleistungszentrum (DLZ) des Bundesamt für Kartographie und Geodäsie: https://www.bkg.bund.de/DE/Service/Kontakt/kontakt.html. Der Quellenvermerk ist zu beachten.</string>
            </entry>
            <entry>
              <string>en</string>
              <string>This data is protected by copyright. It is provided against payment only. The regulations of the Directive on Fees regarding the Provision and Use of Geographic Reference Data of the Surveying Authorities of the Laender of the Federal Republic of Germany apply (AdV Fee Directive in its current version – AdV-GR: https://www.adv-online.de/Products/Terms-of-purchase/). In order to obtain the rights of use please contact the Central Office for Geotopography of the AdV operated at the Service Centre (DLZ) of the Federal Agency for Cartography and Geodesy: https://www.bkg.bund.de/EN/About-BKG/Service-Center/service-center.html. Please include the required reference to the source when using the data.</string>
            </entry>
          </localisations>
          <data></data>
        </entry>
        <type>UPDATE</type>
        <entry>
          <id>6</id>
          <description></description>
          <localisations>
            <entry>
              <string>de</string>
              <string>Die Daten sind urheberrechtlich geschützt. Sie werden nur gegen Entgelt abgegeben. Es gelten die Regelungen der Richtlinie über Gebühren für die Bereitstellung und Nutzung von Geobasisdaten der Vermessungsverwaltungen der Länder der Bundesrepublik Deutschland (AdV-Gebührenrichtlinie in ihrer jeweils gültigen Fassung – AdV-GR: https://www.adv-online.de/AdV-Produkte/Bezugsbedingungen/). Bundesbehörden und Nutzungsberechtigten im Sinne des § 4 VGeoBund werden die Daten auf Grundlage des Vertrages über die kontinuierliche Übermittlung von amtlichen digitalen Geobasisdaten der Länder zur Nutzung im Bundesbereich vom 01.07.2019 (VGeoBund) zur Verfügung gestellt. Für den Erwerb von Nutzungsrechten wenden Sie sich bitte an die Zentrale Stelle Geotopographie der AdV/Dienstleistungszentrum (DLZ) des Bundesamt für Kartographie und Geodäsie: https://www.bkg.bund.de/DE/Service/Kontakt/kontakt.html. Der Quellenvermerk ist zu beachten.</string>
            </entry>
            <entry>
              <string>en</string>
              <string>This data is protected by copyright. It is provided against payment only. The regulations of the Directive on Fees regarding the Provision and Use of Geographic Reference Data of the Surveying Authorities of the Laender of the Federal Republic of Germany apply (AdV Fee Directive in its current version – AdV-GR: https://www.adv-online.de/Products/Terms-of-purchase/). In accordance with the Contract on the Continuous Transfer of Authoritative Digital Geodata of the Laender for use within the German Federal Administration as published on July 1, 2019 (VGeoBund), the geodata is made available to federal institutions and beneficiaries within the meaning of § 4 VGeoBund. In order to obtain the rights of use please contact the Central Office for Geotopography of the AdV operated at the Service Centre (DLZ) of the Federal Agency for Cartography and Geodesy: https://www.bkg.bund.de/EN/About-BKG/Service-Center/service-center.html. Please include the required reference to the source when using the data.</string>
            </entry>
          </localisations>
          <data></data>
        </entry>
      </de.ingrid.codelistHandler.model.CodeListEntryUpdate>
    </entries>
  </de.ingrid.codelistHandler.model.CodeListUpdate>
</list>
